>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们更深入地看待胁迫
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's take a look
at coercion a bit more deeply with
这次演习
this exercise.
我们已经了解到胁迫是如何运作的
We've learned now a bit
about how coercion works
有不同的运营商，比如运营商和类似的事情。
with different operators, like the less
than operator and things like that.
所以我们想做一些验证功能来确保一些输入
So we wanna do some validation functions
to make sure that some inputs that
即将到来，例如在来自 DOM 输入的 Web 页面上，
are coming, for example on a Web page
that are coming from DOM inputs,
我们要确保用户向我们提供的某些输入有效。
we want to make sure that some inputs
that the user is giving to us are valid.
因此，我们将定义两个不同的验证器函数。
So we're going to define two
different validator functions.
第一个称为 isValidName。
The first one's called isValidName.
它给出了此处的需求，需要获取一个字符串，
And it gives the requirements here,
needs to take a string that is
非空，必须包含非空格的内容，
non-empty, must contain something
that's not white space,
至少要长三个字好吗
and has to be at least three
characters long, okay?
所以如果你通过的是什么，它就必须归还。
So it has to return true if what
you pass in matches that, and
否则返回 false。
otherwise return false.
而这次演习的精神是
And again, the spirit of this exercise is,
利用我们现在学到的手段来妥善处理这个问题
use what we've learned now about
coercion to properly handles this.
所以有各种各样的方法去做，但是试图正确处理这一检查。
So there's a variety of ways to do it,
but try to properly handle that check.
然后你会做一个稍微复杂一些的验证器，叫做 " hoursAttended" 。
Then you're gonna do a slightly more
complex validator called hoursAttended.
它需要两个输入，我们会给他们打电话和长度。
It takes two inputs,
we'll call them attended and length.
它允许其中一个为字符串或数字。
It allows either one of these
to be a string or a number.
所以我们会在这里进行一些胁迫。
So we are gonna allow
a bit of coercion here.
我们不会说它永远是个数字
We're not gonna say it has
to always be a number.
我们将允许字符串和数字，但不允许其他内容。
We'll allow both strings and
numbers, but nothing else.
所以我们得检查清楚
So we need to check to make sure, or
假设这些都是字符串和数字
assume that those are definitely
strings and numbers.
不管他们是否以数字来做，我们会把他们当作数字来对待。
Whether they come in as numbers or not,
we're going to treat them as numbers.
因此，如果你错了，这不是我们抛出的断言。
So this is not a case we throw
an assertion if you pass it wrong.
我们只是说这里的合同是你得把这个当作绳子
We're just gonna say the contract here is,
you've gotta pass this as a string or
数字，然后将其视为数字。
a number, and then treat it as a number.
这些数字必须是 0 或更高，因此没有负数。
Those numbers have to be 0 or
higher, so no negative numbers.
而且，它们必须是整数。
And also, they have to be whole numbers.
我们不想在 3 . 14 之类的地方过去好吗
We don't wanna pass in
something like 3.14, okay?
最后，出席的时间必须小于或等于长度。
And then, finally, attended has to
be less than or equal to length.
这就是你要定义的两个验证器
So those are your two validators
that you're gonna define,
试图实践我们迄今为止在胁迫方面学到的东西
trying to practice what we've learned so
far about coercion.
我们会花十分钟的时间
We'll take about ten minutes on this.
正如你在练习文件中看到的那样
As you can see in the exercise file,
我们有 console.log 语句，本质上是我们的测试用例。
we have console.log statements which
are our test cases, essentially.
这是穷人的测试方法，如果你愿意的话。
This is the poor man's approach
to testing, if you will.
因此，如果您的功能正确，那么所有这些控制台日志语句都应显示为 true 。
So all these console log statements should
print true if your functions are correct.
定义这两个函数。
Define those two functions.
将此代码放到您喜欢的控制台中，或在节点中运行该代码，
Drop this code into your favorite
console or run it in Node,
你应该把一切都打印好
and you should get it printing all trues.
这次演习约十分钟后我们就会回来
We'll take about ten minutes for this
exercise, and then we'll come back and
谈谈这个解决方案。
talk about the solution.